Guide to Tuli Kupferberg and Sylvia Topp Papers MSS.385
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Cartoons/Collages, 1964, 1970-2008, undated; 20 Linear Feet in .5 record carton, 44 manuscript boxes, 1 flat folder, 3 oversize flat folders, 1 flat-file folder
  - Slave Market, 2002; cuid33589 (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - Book of Perverbs -- Patrick Henry, 2007; cuid33590 (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - Our Arses and Stupidities, 2008; cuid33591 (Box 119, Folder 24)
  - Birds and Bees, 1996; cuid33592 (Box 119, Folder 25)
  - Lucky Jim, 1986-1998; cuid33593 (Box 119, Folder 26)
  - Burn People Not Flags, 1989; cuid33594 (Box 119, Folder 27)
  - Laika, 1996; cuid33595 (Box 119, Folder 28)
  - Space Rat, 1993, 1996; cuid33596 (Box 119, Folder 29)
  - Satellite, 1985; cuid33597 (Box 119, Folder 30)
  - Why Challenger Failed, 1986; cuid33598 (Box 119, Folder 31)
  - Miracles, 1985; cuid33599 (Box 119, Folder 32)
  - Sex, 1998-2000; cuid33600 (Box 119, Folder 33)
  - Sex -- Kid: Fig Leaf X-tra / Gun Naked, 1999; cuid33601 (Box 119, Folder 34)
  - Sex: Jou Jou Bust, 1999; cuid33602 (Box 119, Folder 35)
  - Sex -- Teach Yourself Fucking, circa 1997; cuid33603 (Box 119, Folder 36)
  - Sex -- Scholars All Agree, undated; cuid33604 (Box 119, Folder 37)
  - Sex -- All You Ever Do Is Complain, 1989; cuid33605 (Box 119, Folder 38)
  - Sex -- Wrong About Massachusetts, undated; cuid33606 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Sex -- Form Follows Function, undated; cuid33607 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Sex -- War: Wanna Fuck, undated; cuid33608 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Sex -- Land of Mystery, undated; cuid33609 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Sex -- Hero Worship, undated; cuid33610 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Sex -- Yap-Yum, undated; cuid33611 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Sex -- Admiral Rape, undated; cuid33612 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Sex -- Cocksure, 1985; cuid33613 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Sex -- What's the Rush?, undated; cuid33614 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Sex -- Snakes, 1993; cuid33615 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Sex -- Eve and Adam Wear Clothes So Ashamed, 1995; cuid33616 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Sex -- Mom and Dad, 1989; cuid33617 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Sex -- Old Fucks at Home -- Group Marriage Aids, 1990; cuid33618 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Sex -- I Hate Dykes, 1992; cuid33619 (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Sex -- Let Him Eat Cock, 1990; cuid33620 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Sex -- We Made Love, circa 1997; cuid33621 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Sex -- One Size Fits All, undated; cuid33622 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Sex -- Read My Lips, 1992; cuid33623 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Sex, circa 1980-1999; cuid33624 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Sex -- 104, undated; cuid33625 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Sex -- Old Fucks at Home -- Flirt Globally, undated; cuid33626 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Sex -- Fart Feller, undated; cuid33627 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Sex -- Beast with 2 Flacks, 1990; cuid33628 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Sex -- Phallic Symbol, 1990; cuid33629 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - Sex -- Nympho Maniac, 1993; cuid33630 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Sex -- Pussy Juice, undated; cuid33631 (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Sex -- Old Fucks at Home -- Erotic Baker, 1990; cuid33632 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Sex -- Cynic Stuff, undated; cuid33633 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - Sex -- Safe Sex, undated; cuid33634 (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - Sex -- AIDS OK, 1989; cuid33635 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - Sex -- Sextras, circa 1980s-1990s; cuid33636 (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Sex -- The Chancellor, undated; cuid33637 (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - Sex -- Slept With 100 Women, 1997; cuid33638 (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Automatic Scientists, undated; cuid33639 (Box 120, Folder 34)
  - Dog Raft It!, 1998; cuid33640 (Box 120, Folder 35)
  - Alone at Last, undated; cuid33641 (Box 120, Folder 36)
  - If I Gave You My Money, undated; cuid33642 (Box 120, Folder 37)
  - Sit Up Straight, undated; cuid33643 (Box 120, Folder 38)
  - Great Moments in the History of Marxism, circa 1980-2008; cuid33644 (Box 120, Folder 39)
  - Shoemaker Between Iraq, 2004; cuid33645 (Box 120, Folder 40)
  - Nuclear Age Salute, 2001; cuid33646 (Box 120, Folder 41)
  - Assorted Tuli Kupferberg Cartoons, 2004-2005; cuid33647 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Mine is Proper, circa 1980-2008; cuid33648 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Asses in Midstream, circa 2004-2008; cuid33649 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Labor Daze Carts and CC, circa 1980-2005; cuid33650 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Give War a Chance, 2004; cuid33651 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Che NYer, 2004; cuid33652 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Kill Fraulein?, 1998; cuid33653 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Lefebre, 2003; cuid33654 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Great Moments in the History of the Monarchy -- Tina Brown / Di / Chuck, 1994; cuid33655 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Marcus Aurelius, 2003; cuid33656 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Rubaiyat / Fitzgerald / Myself When Young, 2007; cuid33657 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - You Can...Harvard Man / Old Farts at Home, 1990, 2007; cuid33658 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - A Song A Day, 2008; cuid33659 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - War If Everybody Came, 2008; cuid33660 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Kropotkin, 2008; cuid33661 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Penis Mightier Than Sword, 2007; cuid33662 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Estrogen, circa 1980-2008; cuid33663 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - Electric Cigarettes, 1998; cuid33664 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - Anger is a Fool, 2008; cuid33665 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - Flea Banana, 2008; cuid33666 (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - Whole World is Crazy, 2008; cuid33667 (Box 121, Folder 21)
  - Elections: Traps for Fools, 2008; cuid33668 (Box 121, Folder 22)
  - Shredder, 1994; cuid33669 (Box 121, Folder 23)
  - Marx at British Museum Xmas Eve, 2008; cuid33670 (Box 121, Folder 24)
  - The New Cabinet, circa 1980-2008; cuid33671 (Box 121, Folder 25)
  - Assorted Book of Perverbs and Miscellaneous, circa 1980-2008; cuid33672 (Box 121, Folder 26)
  - Crazy Journalists, 2007; cuid33673 (Box 121, Folder 27)
  - My Ol' President Lied Over the Ocean, 2008; cuid33674 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - There is a House in New York Town / They Call the "Stock Exchange", 2008; cuid33675 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Go to the Sluggard Thou Ant, 2008; cuid33676 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - First Thot, 2007; cuid33677 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Presidents Annex, circa 2006-2008; cuid33678 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Military Presidents, 2003-2004; cuid33679 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Tuli's Sent to Ed / Eds, circa 2007; cuid33680 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Broad: No War, 1998; cuid33681 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Giuliani Considers Running, 2001; cuid33682 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Shitle of Liberty Bomb, 1999; cuid33683 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Kids Directory, 1985; cuid33684 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Perfect Soldier, 2004; cuid33685 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Post-Primate, 1988; cuid33686 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Human Stupidity, 1988; cuid33687 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - What the Hell was That?, circa 1980-2008; cuid33688 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Roasted Turkeys, 2000; cuid33689 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Euripedes, 1998; cuid33690 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Worst Book...Read, circa 1980-2008; cuid33691 (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - Congress of Gold, 2001; cuid33692 (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Cartoons, 1995, 2004; cuid33693 (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - Tobacco Miscellany, circa 1980-2008; cuid33694 (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Opium Wars, circa 1995; cuid33695 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Marine Xmas Toys for Tots, 1987; cuid33696 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Flow My Country Tis of Thee, 1991; cuid33697 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Welcome to Cancerville, circa 1980-2008; cuid33698 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Salute to Kool, 1985; cuid33699 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Looters, circa 1992-2008; cuid33700 (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, circa 1980-2008; cuid33701 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Work / Source Material, 1983-1987; cuid33702 (Box 123, Folder 8-9)
  - Crawford and Tuli, 1982; cuid33703 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Prizes, 1997; cuid33704 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Child Labor, 1977-1994, undated; cuid33705 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Kosher Dog Food, 1995; cuid33706 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Fucking Animals!, undated; cuid33707 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Incest, 1984; cuid33708 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Lennon -- Goldman, 1988; cuid33709 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Pornography -- Adolescent Sexuality, 1989; cuid33710 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Dick, circa 1980-2008; cuid33711 (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - Henry Miller was a Prick, 1991; cuid33712 (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - Washington Monuments, 1988; cuid33713 (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - Old Fucks at Home -- Blow on It, 1990; cuid33714 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - It's All Been Said, circa 1980-2008; cuid33715 (Box 123, Folder 22)
  - Headache -- Thank God, circa 1980-2008; cuid33716 (Box 123, Folder 23)
  - Sex -- Wanna Fuck, 1989; cuid33717 (Box 123, Folder 24)
  - Get the Code Book, circa 1980-2008; cuid33718 (Box 123, Folder 25)
  - Want a Fuck?, circa 1980-2008; cuid33719 (Box 123, Folder 26)
  - Anti-Porn Activist, 1987; cuid33720 (Box 123, Folder 27)
  - Yank Pants, 1987; cuid33721 (Box 123, Folder 28)
  - Woman Discovers Man, 1988; cuid33722 (Box 123, Folder 29)
  - Food of Love, 1988; cuid33723 (Box 123, Folder 30)
  - Ladakh, circa 1980-2008; cuid33724 (Box 123, Folder 31)
  - Today -- 1872 cover, circa 1980-2008; cuid33725 (Box 123, Folder 32)
  - Hippies and C, undated; cuid33726 (Box 123, Folder 33)
  - Do You Do Sex? Not Since 60's, circa 1980-2008; cuid33727 (Box 123, Folder 34)
  - Sage -- Koresh, 1993; cuid33728 (Box 123, Folder 35)
  - The 60's Coming Back, 1993; cuid33729 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Sri Garneesh Godchoy, circa 1980-2008; cuid33730 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism -- 60's are Over, 1994; cuid33731 (Box 124, Folder 3-4)
  - Berrigan Bros, 1984; cuid33732 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Beautiful Woman / Village Voice, 1984; cuid33733 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Sports / Single Mother, circa 1980-2008; cuid33734 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Sports -- Boxing, circa 1980-2008; cuid33735 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Sports -- Philosophy of Baseball, 1998; cuid33736 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Sports -- Mountain Idiots / Everest, 1992, 2001; cuid33737 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Sports -- Spartans Invent Football, 1986; cuid33738 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Sports -- Moral Equipment of War, circa 1980-2008; cuid33739 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Sports -- Wanna Thank Jesus, circa 1980-2008; cuid33740 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Sports -- Football, 1984; cuid33741 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Sports -- Good Training for Sport, circa 1980-2008; cuid33742 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Sports -- T-Shirt -- Village Voice, circa 1981; cuid33743 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Sati, 1987; cuid33744 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Figment of Imagination, circa 1980-2008; cuid33745 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - I Forgot to Have a Life, circa 1986-2008; cuid33746 (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - Fuck Snakes, 1989; cuid33747 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - Fuck Ya! In Big Trouble, 1989; cuid33748 (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - God Proposes / Woman Disposes, 1989; cuid33749 (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - Incentive, 1983-1984; cuid33750 (Box 124, Folder 23)
  - Eat Fish, circa 1980-2008; cuid33751 (Box 124, Folder 24)
  - Why? Wha Happened, 1985, 1996; cuid33752 (Box 124, Folder 25-26)
  - Dick of Occup Titles, 1996; cuid33753 (Box 124, Folder 27)
  - Nobody Wants to Work, circa 1980-2008; cuid33754 (Box 124, Folder 28)
  - Schickl Gruber Mgmt, 1993; cuid33755 (Box 124, Folder 29)
  - He's a Pedestrian, 1993; cuid33756 (Box 124, Folder 30)
  - Havemeyer Smack Smack, circa 1980-2008; cuid33757 (Box 124, Folder 31)
  - Gets the Sack with All the Rest, circa 1980-2008; cuid33758 (Box 124, Folder 32)
  - Capitalist Corps, 1988; cuid33759 (Box 124, Folder 33)
  - Inferiyer, circa 1980-2008; cuid33760 (Box 124, Folder 34)
  - Waiter, 1987; cuid33761 (Box 124, Folder 35)
  - Lech Walesa, 1989; cuid33762 (Box 124, Folder 36)
  - Karlo Gitarlo, circa 1990-2010; cuid33763 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Jingle Ass, circa 1990-2010; cuid33764 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Easy to Pick Up, circa 1990-2010; cuid33765 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Beatles: Great Moments in the History of Music, circa 1995-1998; cuid33766 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Writers Block, circa 1990-2010; cuid33767 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Lesbian Satan, 2008; cuid33768 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Ideal Boy, circa 1990-2010; cuid33769 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Sorority Sluts, circa 1990-2010; cuid33770 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Problem (Rich) Girl, circa 1990-2010; cuid33771 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Doctors, 1995; cuid33772 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Diet Smoker, circa 1990-2010; cuid33773 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Beatles Photos, circa 1990-2010; cuid33774 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - You've Broken Yours, circa 1990-2010; cuid33775 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Beer / Dancin', circa 1990-2010; cuid33776 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Smoke Yr Life Away, 1996-2000; cuid33777 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - 3 Stooges, 2000; cuid33778 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Go Fuck Myself, 1998; cuid33779 (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - Bad Habits, circa 1990-2010; cuid33780 (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - Knickers, 2007; cuid33781 (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - Karl Get a Job, 1996-2006; cuid33782 (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - Kitchen Crap, circa 1990-2010; cuid33783 (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - Doctors, circa 1996; cuid33784 (Box 125, Folder 22)
  - Anything You Can Do / I Can Do Better, 2004-2007; cuid33785 (Box 125, Folder 23)
  - Menand, 2007; cuid33786 (Box 125, Folder 24)
  - You Can't Fool Me -- I'm Too Ignorant, 2007; cuid33787 (Box 125, Folder 25)
  - Jew Nose, circa 1997-2010; cuid33788 (Box 125, Folder 26)
  - Talk Enough, 2000; cuid33789 (Box 125, Folder 27)
  - Elvis, circa 1990-2010; cuid33790 (Box 125, Folder 28)
  - Yellow Submarine Beatles, circa 1990-2010; cuid33791 (Box 125, Folder 29)
  - Beatles / Hard Days Night, circa 1990-2010; cuid33792 (Box 125, Folder 30)
  - Love Not War, 2006; cuid33793 (Box 125, Folder 31)
  - Iraq, circa 1990-2010; cuid33794 (Box 125, Folder 32)
  - Cures, Aches and Pains, circa 1990-2010; cuid33795 (Box 125, Folder 33)
  - Something Hot Inside, circa 1990-2010; cuid33796 (Box 125, Folder 34)
  - NY Scenic Tours, circa 1990-2010; cuid33797 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - 2 Cat Love, circa 1990-2010; cuid33798 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Fairy, circa 1990-2010; cuid33799 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Savage Bride, circa 1990-2010; cuid33800 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 2006; cuid33801 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Strange Behavior at Work Again, circa 1990-2010; cuid33802 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Karlo Cigarlo, 2007; cuid33803 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Dog Piss, circa 1990-2010; cuid33804 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Les Marx Brothers, circa 1990-2010; cuid33805 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Lawyers, circa 1990-2010; cuid33806 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - One Girl's Confession, circa 1988-2010; cuid33807 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Jesus is Coming, circa 1990-2010; cuid33808 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Keep Smiling Boss Loves Idiots, 1985; cuid33809 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Lonesome Mark Twain, circa 1990-2010; cuid33810 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Untitled, circa 1990-2010; cuid33811 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - It's Hard Out There for a Chimp, 2006; cuid33812 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Freud, circa 1990-2010; cuid33813 (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Woman Who Knows, circa 1990-2010; cuid33814 (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - Karl / Guitarist, circa 1990-2010; cuid33815 (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - Red Karl and Black, circa 1990-2010; cuid33816 (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - Great Moments in Marxism on Tottenham Court Road, circa 1990-2010; cuid33817 (Box 126, Folder 21)
  - Play It Again Karl, 2003-2004; cuid33818 (Box 126, Folder 22)
  - Karl Satanist, 1998-2001; cuid33819 (Box 126, Folder 23)
  - Sex a Go Go, circa 1990-2010; cuid33820 (Box 126, Folder 24)
  - Slept With 5 Presidents, 1992, 1996; cuid33821 (Box 126, Folder 25)
  - Sperm a Good Idea, 1995; cuid33822 (Box 126, Folder 26)
  - Dial M for Man, circa 1990-2010; cuid33823 (Box 126, Folder 27)
  - Beer, Sex or Drugs, circa 1990-2010; cuid33824 (Box 126, Folder 28)
  - Like Crazy Man, circa 1997-2010; cuid33825 (Box 126, Folder 29)
  - Pears, 2004; cuid33826 (Box 126, Folder 30)
  - Blaue Engel Marlene, circa 1990-2010; cuid33827 (Box 126, Folder 31)
  - Beware of Boss, circa 1990-2010; cuid33828 (Box 126, Folder 32)
  - You Are Right!, circa 1990-2010; cuid33829 (Box 126, Folder 33)
  - BS, circa 1990-2010; cuid33830 (Box 126, Folder 34)
  - American Sensibility, 2000; cuid33831 (Box 126, Folder 35)
  - Dylan, Don't Look Back, circa 1990-2010; cuid33832 (Box 126, Folder 36)
  - Pear's Soap, circa 1990-2010; cuid33833 (Box 126, Folder 37)
  - Annie, circa 1990-2010; cuid33834 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - The 60's Around?, 2005-2010; cuid33835 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Lez, circa 1990-2010; cuid33836 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Once A German, circa 1990-2010; cuid33837 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Tunnel, circa 1990-2010; cuid33838 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Klub Weimar, circa 1990-2010; cuid33839 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Atrocious Judges, circa 1990-2010; cuid33840 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Video: A Xmas Fantasy, 2008; cuid33841 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Wentworth Dillon, 2008; cuid33842 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Autonomedia, circa 1990-2010; cuid33843 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Arawak Massacre, circa 1990-2010; cuid33844 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - When We Were First Married, circa 1990-2010; cuid33845 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Carnal Knowledge, 2008; cuid33846 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - War and Peace, 1998-2008; cuid33847 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - From: Listen to the Mockingbird, circa 1990-2010; cuid33848 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Each Day Better Thank the Next, 2008; cuid33849 (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - Kostelanetz, 2009; cuid33850 (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - A Fool and His Money are Soon President, circa 1990-2010; cuid33851 (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - The Lord is a Man of War, circa 1990-2010; cuid33852 (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - Hey Ma: Look at Me!, 2008; cuid33853 (Box 127, Folder 20)
  - You Can't Fool Me I'm Too Ignorant, 2002; cuid33854 (Box 127, Folder 21)
  - I Take Reading, circa 1990-2010; cuid33855 (Box 127, Folder 22)
  - There's Been a Warning About Global Warming, 2007; cuid33856 (Box 127, Folder 23)
  - Mane An Ass of Yourself, 2006-2007; cuid33857 (Box 127, Folder 24)
  - You Wait Ages for a Bust and Then Three Come Along At Once, circa 1990-2010; cuid33858 (Box 127, Folder 25)
  - Get Wisdom, circa 1990-2010; cuid33859 (Box 127, Folder 26)
  - Oscar Wilde, circa 1990-2010; cuid33860 (Box 127, Folder 27)
  - Any Bombs Today, Tune: Any Bads Today, circa 1990-2010; cuid33861 (Box 127, Folder 28)
  - Engels Illus at 19? To: Minor Poet From The Lower East Side, circa 1990-2010; cuid33862 (Box 127, Folder 29)
  - Sound of Weeping, 2004; cuid33863 (Box 127, Folder 30)
  - Book of Perverbs -- Of Making Many Books, circa 1990-2010; cuid33864 (Box 127, Folder 31)
  - Napo Bush, circa 1990-2010; cuid33865 (Box 127, Folder 32)
  - Celebrex, 2006; cuid33866 (Box 127, Folder 33)
  - Fartology, 2006; cuid33867 (Box 127, Folder 34)
  - Toothpaste Patriot, circa 1990-2010; cuid33868 (Box 127, Folder 35)
  - Lili Marlene, 2006; cuid33869 (Box 127, Folder 36)
  - Your Brain on Capitalism, circa 1983-2010; cuid33870 (Box 127, Folder 37)
  - Baby Jumper, circa 1990-2010; cuid33871 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Wir Wahlen Hindendurg, 2001; cuid33872 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Hatchet Face, circa 1990-2010; cuid33873 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Army Clothes, circa 1990-2010; cuid33874 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Sport Q's II National Lampoon, circa 1988; cuid33875 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - The Change is Forever, 2003; cuid33876 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Med Bux, circa 1990-2010; cuid33877 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - My Own Bag, circa 2003-2010; cuid33878 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Homestead Strike, 1978-2003; cuid33879 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - And for Those Who Have Nothing, 2008; cuid33880 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Together Again for the First Time, 2008; cuid33881 (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Smart Bomb, 2003; cuid33882 (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - 5 -- Armaments Fair, undated; cuid33883 (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - The Mexicans are Doomed to Fail, 2005-2006; cuid33884 (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - America Number 1, 1998, 2007, undated; cuid33885 (Box 128, Folder 15)
  - Britannia Waves the Rules, 2004-2007; cuid33886 (Box 128, Folder 16)
  - Book of Perverbs -- Loitering, 2007; cuid33887 (Box 128, Folder 17)
  - Fuck Obscenity, undated; cuid33888 (Box 128, Folder 18)
  - John Wayne the Camel, circa 1995-2010; cuid33889 (Box 128, Folder 19)
  - Flesh and Paper, 1996; cuid33890 (Box 128, Folder 20)
  - Book of Perverbs -- Global Warning, undated; cuid33891 (Box 128, Folder 21)
  - Pity the Nation -- Lawrence Ferlinghetti, 2007; cuid33892 (Box 128, Folder 22)
  - Soldier as Stick, 2007; cuid33893 (Box 128, Folder 23)
  - I've Been Working for the Landlord, undated; cuid33894 (Box 128, Folder 24)
  - Invest-A-Death, 1999; cuid33895 (Box 128, Folder 25)
  - Found Poem NYC, 1960s -- Do In Color, circa 1960s; cuid33896 (Box 128, Folder 26)
  - Remove Unwanted Hair, 1998; cuid33897 (Box 128, Folder 27)
  - One Pope, undated; cuid33898 (Box 128, Folder 28)
  - Venus, undated; cuid33899 (Box 128, Folder 29)
  - Vocal Gymnastics, undated; cuid33900 (Box 128, Folder 30)
  - When the Beer Was Good, undated; cuid33901 (Box 128, Folder 31)
  - Etiquette Ashore, undated; cuid33902 (Box 128, Folder 32)
  - Virginia Woolf's Truth, 1991, 1997; cuid33903 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Postage Stamps, undated; cuid33904 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Music $ [from 1930], undated; cuid33905 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Einstein vs. War, 1999; cuid33906 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Every Minute 30 Children Die, 1995; cuid33907 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Heinrich Ze Eighth, undated; cuid33908 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - M and My Job at the RR Office, undated; cuid33909 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Rome, 1992, 1996; cuid33910 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Book of Perverbs -- Rome Wasn't Burned, 1989-1997, undated; cuid33911 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Begging Revision, 1996, 1998; cuid33912 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Blast from the Past, 1951, undated; cuid33913 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - O'Rourke, circa 1995; cuid33914 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Next Draft, 1999; cuid33915 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Unhealthy Societies, 1999; cuid33916 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Bob Hope, 1998; cuid33917 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Fearomoans, 1999; cuid33918 (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - America You Stink, undated; cuid33919 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Slogans, 1990, undated; cuid33920 (Box 129, Folder 18)
  - Black Man and Chicken -- Nobody Here But Us Racists, undated; cuid33921 (Box 129, Folder 19)
  - Great Moments in the History of Capitalism -- At the Old Batsgame, 1997, 1999; cuid33922 (Box 129, Folder 20)
  - Mayan Sacrifice, 1999; cuid33923 (Box 129, Folder 21)
  - Selling Patients, 1999; cuid33924 (Box 129, Folder 22)
  - Serbian War, 1999; cuid33925 (Box 129, Folder 23)
  - Sleaze J (Dickens), 1993-1997; cuid33926 (Box 129, Folder 24)
  - Possibles, 1997, undated; cuid33927 (Box 129, Folder 25)
  - Hello Da(llar)lie, 1998; cuid33928 (Box 129, Folder 26)
  - Book of Perverbs -- Spinach, undated; cuid33929 (Box 129, Folder 27)
  - Gray, Alasdair, 1991; cuid33930 (Box 129, Folder 28)
  - Great Moments in the History of Film -- Benigni, 1999; cuid33931 (Box 129, Folder 29)
  - Aztecas Sacrifice, undated; cuid33932 (Box 129, Folder 30)
  - Royalty, 1999; cuid33933 (Box 129, Folder 31)
  - The Mild Power Subdues, undated; cuid33934 (Box 129, Folder 32)
  - Oy America!, 2001, 2006; cuid33935 (Box 129, Folder 33)
  - Beware of Boss, undated; cuid33936 (Box 129, Folder 34)
  - Like a Song, undated; cuid33937 (Box 129, Folder 35)
  - Us Poets, undated; cuid33938 (Box 129, Folder 36)
  - GIs Do the Same, 2004; cuid33939 (Box 129, Folder 37)
  - Music, 1995, 2002; cuid33940 (Box 129, Folder 38)
  - Careless War, 2006; cuid33941 (Box 129, Folder 39)
  - Go Down Congress, undated; cuid33942 (Box 129, Folder 40)
  - 4 Insurgent Jews -- Illust. / What a Jew We Have in Jesus, undated; cuid33943 (Box 129, Folder 41)